parcelled.in 2016-11-28

# 

We at Parcelled are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.parcelled.in. This includes information provided when subscribing to our newsletter, posting material or requesting further services.

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence together with your name, address and phone number.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

#### What we do with the information we collect

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To improve our products and services.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by email, post or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way please send an email with your request to support@parcelled.in

#### Where we store your personal data

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure third party servers.

Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site and stored on our third party servers; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

#### Your consent and rights of access

We will only collect and store information about you, with your consent. You give us your consent by choosing to opt in or out on the application form and also by reading and acknowledging you have read and understood the “Privacy Policy” when placing an order.

If any data or information we hold about you is inaccurate or out of date then please let us know and this will be corrected immediately.

You can change your mind or remove or add your consent at any time and you can be removed from our database. Please note that this will not delete information held about you on other third party databases or information which we are required to hold for legal or regulatory purposes.

You can contact us through the information available on our website for any queries.

#### Cookies

In this section you will find information on what cookies may be set when you visit our website and how to reject or delete those cookies.

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are provided on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example your computer or mobile phone. This information consists of small files known as cookies and they cannot be used to identify you personally.

These pieces of information are used to improve our services for you through, for example:

1\. Enabling a service to recognise your device so you don’t have to provide the same information several times during one task.

2\. Recognising that you may already have provided a username and password so you don’t need to do it for every web page requested.

3\. Measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there’s enough capacity to ensure they’re fast.

#### How to control and delete cookies

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our website or any other website, you can do this through your browser settings.

Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact the functionality of the websites you visit.

Third party cookies

#### Cookies set for embedded social web content

To support our information provision and engagement, we sometimes embed photos and video content from websites such as Youtube, Linkedin, Twitter, Facebook and Flickr. As a result, when you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, Facebook or Twitter, you may be presented with cookies from these websites. We do not control the use of these cookies. You should check third party websites for more information on these cookies.

Our website may also carry embedded ‘share’ buttons to enable users of the site to easily share articles with their peers through a number of popular social networks. These sites may set a cookie when you are also logged in to or otherwise using their service. We have no control over these cookies and you should check for more info from their website on these cookies. 

#### Changes to our privacy policy

This policy was last updated on the 03/11/2014. Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

#### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to support@parcelled.in
